<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Xiaotong Li</title><link>https://emifc.github.io/lixt/</link><description>Recent content on Xiaotong Li</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 12:34:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://emifc.github.io/lixt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Meditation reflection</title><link>https://emifc.github.io/lixt/posts/meditation_feedback/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 12:34:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://emifc.github.io/lixt/posts/meditation_feedback/</guid><description>(1) Today, I tried a new techniques of meditation and I found it helpful to anxiety. Anxiety normally manifests as a sensation between my throat and stomach, so the technique of the middle way meditation - focusing the center of body becomes a very difficult task for me, bringing difficulties to breathing. The imaginary center object and the feeling of anxiety have a war moment, creating a tense, uncomfortable struggle. The thing I tried is, I imagined the center object as resilient, I visualized it transforming into a capsule resting in my mouth.</description></item><item><title>Untitled</title><link>https://emifc.github.io/lixt/posts/untitled/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 12:34:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://emifc.github.io/lixt/posts/untitled/</guid><description>We walked in a private garden, the green moss on the path has the color like I can only find in a painting. They grew in a way of hugging, even though they are individual units, but they seem like an organism, so real and connected. River and I kept walking until we saw two divided straight paths in front of us. We chose the right-side one and biked forward, this path is very well planned, those organized wood at the side to create the division, it looks never-ending and continues to the edge of the planet until we can touch the sky.</description></item><item><title>把真相放在一个空间里</title><link>https://emifc.github.io/lixt/posts/%E6%8A%8A%E7%9C%9F%E7%9B%B8%E6%94%BE%E5%9C%A8%E4%B8%80%E4%B8%AA%E7%A9%BA%E9%97%B4%E9%87%8C/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 12:34:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://emifc.github.io/lixt/posts/%E6%8A%8A%E7%9C%9F%E7%9B%B8%E6%94%BE%E5%9C%A8%E4%B8%80%E4%B8%AA%E7%A9%BA%E9%97%B4%E9%87%8C/</guid><description>昨天看到一些“线索”产生了一种不愉快的感觉，在第二天醒来后，突然有了不同的感受，让我不愉快的“线索” 居然是别人太愉快， 我在想我能永远占有多大部分的一个人的愉悦呢？我想到真相这个词，在仁波切的一个讲坛中他说，人要怔悟最重要的是看到一个真相，一个清醒的真相。我当时提炉灌顶， 有时候还是会忘记这个提炉灌顶的感觉。我的人生应该是开阔于看到真相，我做任何事物的目标也应该如此。对我来说真相是什么，我在想，真相是…地图。我想象一个实体的3d空间，我和真相有三步之遥，首先我需要看到它，它是真的，无法因我而改变的一个真实的实物。它可能对我而言非常丑陋，然后我需要由我发挥，由我感受如何设定我和这个真相的距离，当然也会有很多其他真相在我附近，有的和我的喜好一致，我则离它更近。但有个事情我想提醒自己，我的能量也是我在和这些真相玩乐的一个指标，我需要多少能量能靠近这个真相或那个真相。然后还有观察，虽然总的来说真理只有一个，但是真相有时候也许是变动的，可能会因为判断的不对而变动但是变动时观察到然后调整和真相的距离也是可以的。想到这里，突然感觉无所畏惧。</description></item><item><title>Images I like</title><link>https://emifc.github.io/lixt/posts/photosilike/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://emifc.github.io/lixt/posts/photosilike/</guid><description>Seeing my first ibex!</description></item><item><title>Lede</title><link>https://emifc.github.io/lixt/posts/lede/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://emifc.github.io/lixt/posts/lede/</guid><description>The begining of 2025, I went to a meditation retreat in a Thai temple in Lede, Belguim. There are thoghts during the trip.
Today, during the wisdom talk, the monk said meditation can help rid us of greed and anger—things that make us feel disconnected and lead to suffering. I asked if we can truly get rid of the things that make us suffer, given that they are just expressions of a deeper fear within everyone.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Punker-the magic cat</title><link>https://emifc.github.io/lixt/posts/lucy-punker/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://emifc.github.io/lixt/posts/lucy-punker/</guid><description>Lucy Punker was born in Het Wilde Weg, Sint-Oedenrode, The Netherlands. We met each other during the residency HopePunk: Reknitting Collective Infrastructures of Hackers &amp;amp; Designers in 2023. She named by her pervious family, and her family name is in memory of the residency HopePunk. She has a sister name Laura and a uncle named Harry. Her mother was a bit shy, so I didn&amp;rsquo;t speak to her much, and her father seemed to be missing.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://emifc.github.io/lixt/posts/advanced-usage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://emifc.github.io/lixt/posts/advanced-usage/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Homepages</title><link>https://emifc.github.io/lixt/posts/marked-links/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://emifc.github.io/lixt/posts/marked-links/</guid><description>This page is for the homepages and media I enjoy. And the image on the right for this page is a cap&amp;rsquo;n crunch whistle, seemed as early hacking tool in hacker history.
Tech Learning Collective: https://techlearningcollective.com/ The Atlantic Cable website: https://atlantic-cable.com/#gsc.tab=0 FTL design: https://ftldesign.com/ Mass Observation Archive: https://massobs.org.uk/ Low tech magazine: https://solar.lowtechmagazine.com/ HTML Energy: https://html.energy/ Radar.squat: https://radar.squat.net/en Calculating Empires: https://calculatingempires.net/ Celtic Music Archives: https://tinwhistler.com/ Virtual Borders by Manu Luksch: https://vimeo.com/282580968 犴达罕 The Last Moose Of Aoluguya: https://youtu.</description></item></channel></rss>